最新的血清结果超出预期
The latest serum has surpassed expectations.
测试目标接受血清后…
The test subject has grown five times normal size…
数日内就长到正常的五倍大
…within days of the serum being introduced into its system.
唯一已知的副作用是攻击行为
But the only known side effect is aggressive behaviour…
需要持续喂食 以维持较高的新陈代谢率
…that requires constant feeding to maintain a higher metabolic rate.
目前 目标需要保持镇静
For now, constant sedation of the subject is needed…
不过结果是大有可为的
…but the results are very promising.
只有一种状况会再生
Regeneration only occurs…
就是在受伤部位立即注入血清
…when there is immediate introduction of the serum into the wounded area.
我过去尝试挽救老旧已分解…
My past attempts to save older decomposed…
或严重受损的组织都失败了
…or severely damaged tissue have failed.
血兰花最新的基因改造
The latest genetic modifications to the black-orchid strain…
对血清萃取液有预期性的效果
…have had the predicted effect on the serum extract.
血清现在成功提供显著效益
The serum now successfully provides the apparent benefit…
暂停活组织的分解
…of halting decomposition of living tissue.
这只要适当应用的话
This, of course, would rev olutionise medicine…
在医学上会有革命性的进展
…if properly applied.
《狂蟒之灾4：血路斑驳》
莫达克先生在等您 这边请
Mr. Murdoch is expecting you. Right this way, sir.
进来
Come in.
抱歉 打扰您 尤金先生到了
Sir, sorry to disturb you. Mr. Eugene has arrived.
- 请他进来 - 好的
- Send him in. - Right away, sir.
请进
Come in, please.
您好
Sir.
那里有只手提箱 打开看看
There's a briefcase over there. Have a look inside.
那里是一百万
That's $1 million.
帮我一个小忙 钱就是你的了
It's yours if you'll do a little job for me.
- 我在听 - 坐下
- I'm listening. - Sit.
离这儿不远的森林里有间木屋
There's a cottage in a forest not far from here…
我的员工在那里做实验
…where an employee of mine has been conducting certain experiments…
实验结果可能对我的健康有利
…the outcome of which may be beneficial to my health.
不过是这样的
But here's the thing.
我们跟他失联了 他似乎失踪了
We've lost contact with him. He appears to have disappeared.
- 他实验成功了吗？ - 我相信是
- His experiments were successful? - I believe so.
我相信他创造了新品种的血兰花
I believe he created a new hybrid of the blood orchid…
从中萃取血清 血清奏效了
…extracted a serum from it, and that the serum works.
所以他闹失踪
And that's why he's gone missing…
因为他找到别的老板了
…because he has found another employer.
我要你去收回植栽
Now, I want you to collect all the plant material…
血清和他所有的研究笔记
…the serum, all his research notes.
- 找到他并干掉他 - 就他一个人？
- Find him and kill him. - Just one man?
我要提醒你
I should warn you…
有人说他是地球上最聪明的人
…that some say he's one of the smartest men on the planet.
他可能有几把刷子
He may have one or two tricks up his sleeve.
这么多钱只杀一个人
This is a lot of money for one man.
这项计划我投资了五千万
I have invested over $50 million in this project…
收益无可估计
…and the returns could be incalculable.
不计代价我都要得到结果
I want results no matter what the cost.
还有一件事
One other thing.
照片上的女孩也有参与计划
There's a photo of a girl in there who is also involved with the project.
她知道的太多了
She knows too much.
要是她碍手碍脚
Should she cross your path…
就除掉她
…remove her from the equation.
乐意之至
It would be my pleasure.
正合我意
That's what I wanted to hear.
还有一件事
One other thing.
时间非常重要
Time is of the essence.
我有骨癌
I have bone cancer.
没有这杯小东西
Without this little concoction…
我活不到下个礼拜
…I would be dead within the week.
新的血清会有所改变？
And that new serum might change that?
希望如此
Well, that is my hope.
再见了 先生
Until I see you, sir.
一路顺风
Good hunting.
（喀尔巴阡山 东欧）
这我怎么看得懂啊？
How the heck am I supposed to read this?
年轻人
Hey, you.
你迷路了？
You lost?
没关系 他们是警官
Oh, no, no, it's okay, we're… They're officers.
我搞不清楚方向 地图写的是罗马尼亚文
Well, I got a little turned around. The map's in Romanian.
我看到那里有东西 很大的东西
You know, I saw something out there. Something big.
等等 是看到还是听到？
Wait, you see it or hear it?
都有
Both.
不如你跟着我们吧？
All right, well, why don't you just stick with us, okay?
你怎么会来这里？
So, what's your story?
我暑假来陪祖母
I spend the summers with my grandmother.
她住在附近的小镇 你们都是警察？
She lives in a town nearby. Are you guys all cops?
我不是 我研究花
I'm not. I study flowers.
花？让两个警察陪你？
Flowers? And you have two cops with you?
你来做什么？
What are you doing out here?
我想研究古病理学
Well, I'm studying for a career in palaeopathology.
镇上的人告诉我 这片山区有在做考古挖掘
People in town told me there was a dig going on in these mountains…
所以我想去看一看
…so I wanted to check it out.
- 古什么学？ - 研究古人类遗骸
- Palaeo what? - The study of human ancient remains.
没关系 我朋友也不懂
Yeah, it's okay, my friends don't understand it either.
等一下
Wait. Wait a sec.
- 听到了吗？ - 没有
- You hear that? - No.
森林静悄悄的就表示附近有掠食动物
When the forest goes quiet, there's a predator near.
- 走吧 - 你当真？
- Come on. - Are you serious?
- 你叫什么名字？ - 艾力克斯
- What's your name again? - Alex.
我是阿曼达
I'm Amanda.
你真不应该独自来这里
You know, you really shouldn't be out here alone.
那是什么？
What the hell is that?
各位 我们太暴露了 快去找掩护吧
Listen, you guys, we're too exposed. We need to take cover. Come on.
好
Yeah.
我和那个跩博士在这个考古地点工作 他去休假了
So I'm working this dig with this hotshot Ph. D. Who's on sabbatical.
他开始吹嘘他的新方法
And he starts yapping to me about his new methodology…
还说他发明了工具让他挖得更快
…and how he's developed a tool that allows him to dig faster…
又不会损害到文物
…without damaging any artefacts.
他还告诉我我们的方法是史前方法
He also tells me the way we do it is prehistoric…
别人都不那样做了
…and nobody does it that way anymore.
所以呢？
So?
- 所以我还没说完 - 「我还没说完」
- So I'm not done yet. - "I'm not done yet."
所以这位跩博士把我拉到考古现场
So hotshot, he drags me over to his site.
他跳下洞
He hops down in the hole…
当场用他的新工具
…and he immediately proceeds to chop off two of his fingers…
切断了自己的两根手指头
…with this brand-new tool of his.
这故事有点恐怖 杰克森
That's a bit of a morbid story there, Jackson.
我自己也吓了一跳
I was a little shocked myself.
我有问他是不是 要把那些手指留在现场
I did ask if he was gonna leave fingers…
让未来的人去发掘
…for future generations to uncover.
你是嫉妒他抢先你一步
You were jealous he could out-dig you.
这我不清楚 但他数到三比我快
Well, I don't know about that, but he can count to three faster than me.
好了 大家专心点 我们就快到了
All right, come on, guys, let's focus. We're not too far away.
如果他们所言属实
You know, if what they say is true…
这可能是欧陆最重要的发现
…this could be one of the most important discoveries on the continent.
罗兰 有没有你哥或第一组的消息？
Roland, any news on your brother or Team 1?
没有 没有半点消息
No, haven't heard anything yet.
海瑟 音乐不错听喔
Heather, nice tunes, honey.
- 是啊 - 没错
- Yeah, man. - Yeah.
我忍不住 我是节奏的奴隶
I can't help it. I am a slave to the rhythm.
我是节奏的奴隶
I am a slave to the rhythm.
我想脱衣服
I wanna take my clothes off. I wanna…
我想抚摸你的身体
I wanna touch your body.
太好了 这是我们最不需要的
Great. That's the last thing we need.
有路可以绕道吗？
Any way around it?
- 我看看 - 有人带链锯吗？
- Let me look. - Anyone pack a chain saw?
- 我们可以用石凿 - 在这儿待好几天
- Well, we can use the rock chisels. - Yeah, and we'd be here for days.
没有 只有这条路通往大本营
No, no, this is the only route to the base camp.
可以走山路吗？
Can we go off-road?
我不知道
I don't know.
对 我们可以走山路 不过大概回不来了
Yeah, we could go off. We're not gonna get back on.
好 这样吧
All right, let's break it down.
两天没有第一组的消息
We haven't heard from Team 1 in two days.
从这根木头看来他们没有通过这里
From the looks of this log, they didn't come through here.
我们没有无线电 手机收不到讯号
We've had no radio, no cell-phone communication.
- 猜猜看 我们要用走的 - 你疯了吗？
- Guess what, guys. We're walking. - Are you crazy?
- 杰克森 有五英里耶 - 我们用走的 海瑟
- Jackson, it's five miles, man. - We're walking, Heather.
- 好吧 - 大家听好
- Okay. - Okay, listen up.
去拿背包轻装便行 我们去找第一组
Grab your packs and travel light. We'll get to Team 1.
早上我们再回来用器材搬开这棵树
In the morning, we'll come back, use the equipment to move this tree.
- 杰克森 - 什么事？
- Jackson. - Yeah?
你何不先走？
Why don't you head out now?
我们拿齐了设备再赶上去跟你会合
We'll hunt the rest of the gear and we'll meet you halfway.
- 好 - 好
- All right. - Okay.
- 天很快就黑了 - 那就动作快
- It's getting dark pretty fast. - Well, let's move.
嘿 你们看到了吗？
Hey. Did you see that?
- 什么？ - 听到了吗？
- What? - Did you hear?
什么？
What?
你眼花了
Hey, your eyes are playing tricks on you.
走吧 路可远着呢
Come on. It's been a long drive.
去拿杰克森吉普车上剩下的设备吧
Let's get the rest of the gear out of Jackson's Jeep.
艾力克斯 我们去看看
Hey, Alex, let's go check this out.
- 瓦席里 你们留在这儿 - 好
- Vasile, you guys stay out here. - Okay.
- 要手电筒吗？ - 我有
- Want a flashlight? - I've got one.
天哪 真不敢相信他办到了
Oh, my God, I can't believe he did this.
好多花
Flowers.
不 你不懂 我一直在找这些花
No, you don't understand. I've been looking for these flowers.
混种花 效力可能有两倍
Hybrids, probably twice the potency.
退后
Get back.
你会用这个吗？
Here, you know how to use this?
- 那只是风声吧？ - 也许是
- That was just the wind, right? - Maybe.
- 你在做什么？ - 不要问
- What the hell are you doing? - Don't ask questions.
你要炸掉这个地方？
You're gonna blow this place up?
- 你会用那种东西吗？ - 我知道自己在干嘛
- Do you know how to use that stuff? - I know what I'm doing.
炸掉这些花希望就能做个了结
Put an end to these flowers, hopefully, I'll put an end to it.
- 了结什么？ - 你怎么来的？
- An end to what? - How'd you get here?
- 开吉普车 干嘛？ - 我们会需要它
- My Jeep, why? - We'll need it.
我们要离开一百码我才能炸掉这里
We've gotta get about a 100 yards before I blow this place…
我们走 快点
Let's go, come on.
快 走我前面
Move. Get in front of me. Move.
- 你朋友怎么办？ - 他们可能都死了
- What about your friends? - They're probably dead.
- 阿曼达 这是怎么回事？ - 总之…
- Amanda, what the hell is going on? - Just…
你不懂 继续走就对了
You have no idea. Just keep moving.
继续走 我就在你后面
Keep going, kid. I'm right behind you.
- 你去哪了？ - 就在这儿
- Where the hell were you? - Right here.
快点 找到出口了
Come on, there's a way out.
阿曼达
Amanda.
放心 我去找救兵
Don't worry, I'll get help.
森林静悄悄的就表示附近有掠食动物
If the forest goes quiet, there's a predator near.
嘿
Hey.
哈啰？
Hello?
有人吗？
Guys?
有人在吗？
Is there anybody here?
天哪
Oh, God.
- 杰克森呢？ - 可能迷路了
- Where the hell is Jackson? - Probably lost.
- 他迷路我就宰了他 - 等一下
- I'll kill him if he is. - Wait, wait, wait.
- 干嘛？ - 我看到动静
- What? - I've got movement.
- 在哪？ - 那边
- Where? - Over there.
我什么都没看到
I don't see anything.
好 我过去看看
Okay, I'm gonna check it out.
- 你有带枪？ - 我跟你去
- You brought a gun? - I'll come with you.
- 不要做傻事 - 放心吧
- Don't do anything stupid. - Don't worry.
我们只是去查看一下
We're just gonna check it out.
- 你在做什么？ - 是我 杰克森
- What are you doing, man? - Hey, it's Jackson, it's me.
- 杰克森 - 杰克森
- Jackson. - Jackson.
- 你怎么了？ - 怎么回事？
- What happened to you? - What happened?
- 怎么了？ - 他们死了
- What's wrong? - They're dead.
- 谁死了？ - 什么意思 死了？
- Who's dead? - What do you mean, dead?
- 谁死了？ - 第一组都死了
- Who's dead? - Team 1. They're all dead.
我们快离开这里
Man, we've gotta get out of here.
- 到底是谁死了？ - 什么意思？
- Who's dead exactly? - What do you mean?
我没停下来检查钱包 总之凶手还在那里
I didn't stop and check their wallets. Whatever killed them is still out there.
- 我们走吧 - 冷静点
- Let's go. We gotta go. - Just calm down.
- 太远了 我们去大本营 - 他们就死在大本营！
- We're too far. Let's get to base camp. - They are dead at base camp!
你冷静五秒钟好吗？
Will you calm down five seconds?
我们太深入了 我们要去大本营
Look, we're too far in. We'll get to base camp.
我们至少会有他们的车还有卫星电话
At the least, we'll get their vehicles, get a satellite phone…
做紧急广播
…and send out an emergency broadcast.
- 你错了 - 我是对的 我们太深入了
- You're wrong. - I'm right. We're too far in.
- 快走吧 - 快点
- Now let's move. - Come on.
不
No.
- 快点 - 快啊 我们走
- Come on. - Come on, let's go.
走吧
Come on.
大家不要走散
Everyone stay together.
大家听好
Listen up, ladies.
这是我们的目标 彼得和阿曼达
These are the targets: Peter, Amanda.
赛尔 快点过来
Come on, Sal, join the club. All right.
他在附近的木屋
He's in a cottage near here.
我们找到他 拿到我们要找的东西
We find him, we get what we're looking for…
就清掉房子
…we clean house.
她被列为「见到就杀」
She is classified "shoot on sight."
- 真浪费 - 确实是
- What a waste. - Yes, indeed.
小心点 照我的话去做
Be careful, do as I say…
幸运的话我们天亮前就可以出森林
…and with any luck, we'll be out of the forest by daybreak.
走吧 各位
Come on, gentlemen.
看来我们有伴了
Looks like we've got company.
- 至少是一天前升的火 - 他们的尸体不见了
- This fire's at least a day old. - They're gone. The bodies are gone.
- 没有遗失东西 - 那是好事 对吧？
- There's nothing missing. - That's a good thing, right?
- 也许吧 - 见鬼了
- Maybe. - Like hell it is.
嘿 嘿
Hey. Hey.
今天这里本来有尸体 我亲眼看到的
There were bodies here today. I saw them.
你们为什么就是不信呢？
Now, what about that is not sinking in with you people?
杰克森 没人说你没看到
Jackson, nobody's saying you didn't.
我们都知道第一组可能运尸体去了
For all we know, Team 1 could've been transporting the bodies.
拜托
Oh, come on.
用不着所有人都去运送
It wouldn't take the whole group to take them.
总会有人在这里 他们不会出去工作
Somebody would be here. They're not out working.
我们都知道 他们没有夜间工作的设备
They don't have equipment to work at night.
- 他们在哪里？ - 那我们就去找他们
- Where are they, huh? Where? - Then we have to go looking for them.
- 考古现场在山上 - 我们会去 不过等天亮再去
- The site is up that hill. - And we will, but not until sunup.
今晚不行 我们迷路对他们没好处
Not tonight. We'll be no good to them if we get lost.
- 我自己去 - 你要去 大家就一起去
- I'll go alone. - You go, we all go.
但我告诉你
But let me tell you something.
如果外头有东西
If there is something out there…
晚上它可能会比较占优势
…chances are, it'll have the advantage at night.
- 没错 - 今晚为了保险起见
- True. - Tonight we all play it safe.
大家住一间小屋 轮流站岗
We stay in one hut, and we rotate lookouts.
我知道我有看到
I know what I saw.
杰克森
Jackson.
- 嘿 - 你吓到我了
- Hey. - You scared me.
我想我看到外面有东西
I think I saw something out there.
- 在哪？ - 不知道 那里
- Where? - I don't know, there.
我肯定有听到声音
I must be hearing things.
有看到什么东西吗？
You see anything?
没有 我知道我应该留在屋里
No. I know, I know. I should have stayed inside.
我不知道
I don't know.
我不知道这里是怎么回事
Look, I don't know what's going on here…
但我知道我今天看到了什么
…but I know what I saw today.
我有预感明天会在考古现场发现什么
And I got a pretty good idea of what we're gonna find at the site tomorrow.
我不希望你变成那样
And I don't want you to be a part of that.
明天我要你跟温迪开车回镇上
Tomorrow I want you and Wendy to take the van and go back down.
拜托 为什么？因为我们是女生？
Oh, come on, why? Because we're girls?
不 不是因为你们是女生 这不是什么竞赛
No, no, not because you're girls. Listen, this isn't some kind of contest.
- 对 但是… - 嘿
- Yeah, but… - Hey.
我不希望你出事
I don't want anything to happen to you.
我太在乎你了
I care about you too much.
再提醒我一次 我们为何非得保密不可？
Remind me again, why do we have to keep this a secret?
你知道吗？不用保密
You know what? We don't.
- 不用 对吧？ - 对
- We don't, right? - No.
- 怎么了？ - 有东西咬我
- What? - Something bit me.
- 有东西咬我 - 什么？
- Something bit me. - What?
- 有东西叮了你 - 会刺痛
- Oh, man, something nailed you. - It stings.
- 你还好吧？ - 还好 只是会刺痛
- You okay? - Yeah, it just stings.
- 我们进去找东西把它拿出来 - 好 把它清出来
- Let's go in and get something on that. - Yes, clean it out.
会是什么？你知道吗？
What was it? You got any idea?
你还好吧？
You all right?
不太好
Not really.
艾力克斯
Alex.
艾力克斯？
Alex?
艾力克斯
Alex.
天啊 真不敢相信他逃了
Oh, my God, I can't believe he did this.
嘿
Hey.
Hey there.
你还好吧？
You okay?
不太好
Not so good, no.
- 来吧 - 来什么？
- Let's do this. - Do what?
海瑟 你被游民蜘蛛咬了
Heather, you were bitten by a hobo spider.
它们有毒 但不会致命
They're poisonous, but they're not deadly.
- 好痛 - 我知道 宝贝
- Well, it hurts. - I know it does, honey.
- 但是会过去的 我保证 - 对 最好是
- But it'll pass, I promise. - Yeah, well, it better.
考古现场到处是毒
The area around the bite is filled with poison.
我要切开小伤口把毒放出来
I'm gonna make a tiny incision to drain it out.
这样会让你更快退烧
It'll make your fever drop much quicker.
- 你知道你在干嘛吧？ - 知道
- You know what you're doing, right? - Yeah.
- 我知道自己在干嘛 - 准备好了吗？
- I know what I'm doing. - You ready?
随时来吧
As I'll ever be.
好
Okay.
来吧
Come on. Come on.
- 给你 - 谢谢
- Here. - Thanks.
你不会有事的
You're okay, you're okay.
挺住 不要动
Okay, hang on, hang on.
好 放轻松
Okay, okay. Easy, easy.
没事的
It's okay, it's okay.
不要乱动
Hold still, hold still, hold still.
没事的…
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
她怎么样？
How is she?
- 她没事 亲爱的 - 谢天谢地
- She's fine, honey. - Oh, thank God.
- 有咖啡吗？ - 没有 你可以喝我的
- Got a cup of coffee? - No, but you can have mine.
- 你真好 干杯 - 哪里
- Oh, you're a doll. Cheers. - No problem.
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
我们要去挖掘现场
Listen, we're gonna go to the excavation site…
看能不能找到人
…see if we can find anyone.
温迪会留下来陪你 好吗？
Wendy's gonna stay here with you, okay?
好
Okay.
这个无线电留给你
I'm gonna leave this radio.
你有事找我就打来
If you need to talk to me for any reason, you call, okay?
我在三号频道
I'm on channel three.
准备好了 走吧
They've got it. Let's go.
注意你的体温
Keep an eye on your temperature.
超过102度就打给我
If it goes above a 102, you're gonna call me.
我没事 放心吧
Yeah, I'll be fine. Don't worry.
- 你要打给我喔？ - 别担心
- You're gonna call me, right? - Don't worry.
你在外面小心点 好吗？
Listen, you be careful out there, okay?
好
Yeah.
我不知道会发现什么
I don't know what we're gonna find…
但我会做好最坏的打算
…but I'd be prepared for the worst.
对 看在罗兰的份上 我希望你是错的
Yeah. For Roland's sake, I hope you're wrong.
好极了
Great.
温迪？
Wendy?
这下可好
Oh, great.
温迪？
Wendy?
考古现场应该就在右手边某个地方
The site should be just over there to the right somewhere.
那是哪来的？
Where'd you get that?
- 地图吗？ - 是啊
- What, the map? - Yeah.
在其中一间木屋找到的 肯定是第一组做的
Found it in one of the huts. Team 1 must have made it.
- 不远了对吧？ - 应该是
- It's not much further, right? - Shouldn't be.
我知道你担心你哥
Look, I know you're worried about your brother.
真希望我能上帮忙
And I wish there was something I could do.
他没事 他出事我会有感觉
He's okay. I would feel it if he wasn't.
罗兰、杰克森 快过来
Roland, Jackson, get over here.
天哪 杰克森！史考特！
Oh, my God. Jackson! Scott!
天哪
Oh, God.
过来呀 你这条臭蛇
Come on, you big bag of slime.
糟了
Oh, no.
- 快跑！它在你后面！ - 我知道 快跑
- Run! It's behind you! - I know. Go. Run, come on.
- 听到没有？ - 听到了
- Did you hear that? - Yeah.
从那边传来的
Came from somewhere over there.
罗兰
Roland.
动作快
Move out, move out.
我想前面有块空地
Listen, I think there's a clearing up ahead.
- 搞什么… - 那是什么？
- Son of a… - What is that?
我不是签约来搞这个的
I didn't sign on for this.
搞什么…
What the…
那两个人绝对逃不掉的
Those people are never gonna make it.
我得做点什么
I gotta do something.
- 罗兰 快回来 - 罗兰 不要
- Roland, get back here. - Roland, no.
- 杰克森 - 罗兰 回来
- Jackson… - Roland, get back.
- 杰克森 不要 - 罗兰！
- Jackson, no. - Roland!
杰克森 等等！
Jackson, wait!
- 放开我 - 罗兰！
- God, get off me. - Roland!
- 罗兰！ - 退后…
- Roland! - Back, back.
不要过去 你疯了吗？
No, don't go, don't go. What are you, crazy?
- 快回来啊 - 快点掉头
- Come on, get back here. - Turn around.
罗兰！罗兰 不要！
Roland! Roland, no!
不要！
No!
那是阿曼达 干掉她
That's Amanda. Take her out.
我们无能为力了 走吧
There's nothing we can do. Come on.
- 它来了 - 走 快跑！
- It's coming. - Go, go, run. Run!
那玩意儿怎么办？
What about that thing out there?
它攻击 我们就开枪
If it attacks, we engage.
走
Move.
等等 我们分开跑
Wait, let's split up.
你跟我来 你们走那边
Okay, you, come with me. You guys go that way.
快点
Go, go, go.
温迪 你去哪儿了？
Jeez, Wendy, where were you?
- 我听到后面有人 - 我也听到了
- I heard somebody back there. - Yeah, I heard somebody too.
- 我以为是你 - 你没事吧？
- I thought it was you. - Are you okay?
我没事 我刚醒来…
Yeah, I'm fine, I just woke up and…
- 天哪 - 派崔克！
- Oh, God. - Patrick!
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
- 天哪 派崔克 - 派崔克
- Oh, my God, Patrick. - Patrick.
别说话 放轻松 别开口 什么都别做
Don't say anything. Just relax. Don't speak, don't try anything.
想办法绑紧他的伤口 天哪
Try to tie his wound or something. Oh, my God.
- 冷静点 - 想办法绑紧他的伤口
- Stay calm. - Try and tie his wound.
海瑟 我们需要史考特 快找史考特 我们需要他
Heather, we need Scott. Get Scott. We need him.
- 我去找史考特 - 快 现在就需要他
- I'll go get Scott. I'll call him. - Hurry, we need him right now.
- 等一下 - 撑住 我们找人来帮忙
- Wait. - Hold on, we're getting help.
- 放轻松 冷静点 - 史考特 这里需要你
- Just relax, calm down. - Scott, we need you here.
派崔克回来了 他受伤了
We've got Patrick here. He's injured.
我们需要你 我们没受过这种训练
We need you. We're not trained for this.
天哪 派崔克他… 史考特
Oh, my God. Patrick… Scott.
史考特 请回答 天哪
Scott, please come in, please. Oh, my God.
快 我知道它在后面 它来了
Come on, he's behind us, I know it. He's coming.
- 好 我们混淆它 - 我知道它要来了
- Okay, we'll confuse it. - He's coming, I know he's coming.
你走左边 我们来混淆它
Go left, go left. We'll confuse it.
等那个女的 她才是目标
Wait for the girl. She's the target.
来了
There.
趴下
Get down.
人生辛苦 是吧？
Life is hard, huh?
- 没事 - 那是什么东西？
- It's okay. - What is that?
带我去找你朋友 如果你希望他们平安的话
Your friends, bring me to them if you want them safe. Come on.
有人在吗？有人听到了吗？
Is there anybody out there? Can anybody read me?
快啊 听到了请回答
Come on. Come on. Somebody, anybody, please.
- 完全没响应 - 继续试
- I'm not getting anything. - Keep trying.
- 我在试 他怎么样？ - 不好
- I'm trying. How is he? - Bad.
史考特 请回答
Scott, please, somebody.
有人听到了吗？
Can anybody read me?
- 有人听到了吗？ - 嘿
- Is there anybody out there? Come on. - Hey.
你看
Check it out.
- 拜托 有人听见吗？ - 这是林业局 你在哪里？
- Please, can anyone read me? - Forest Service, what's your location?
- 我收到回应了 - 真的吗？
- I'm getting something. - Really?
我们在玉米田附近的大本营
Yeah, we're at a base camp near a cornfield or something.
我们是在这里工作的考古团队
We're part of the archaeological team working in the area.
- 需要紧急医疗协助… - 温迪！海瑟！
- We need medical help right away. - Wendy! Heather!
杰克森？你到哪儿去了？
Jackson? Where the hell were you?
- 史考特呢？派崔克需要就医 - 天哪
- Where's Scott? Pat needs a medic. - Oh, my God.
天哪
Jesus.
温迪 拿急救箱给我
Wendy, get me the med kit.
- 在你后面的帐蓬里 - 好
- It's in the tent right behind you. - Okay.
- 你没事吧？ - 没事
- Are you okay? - Yeah.
给你
Here you go.
- 让我帮你 - 温迪 去找吉普车的钥匙
- Let me help you. - Find the keys to the Jeep.
- 我们送他离开这里 - 好 我去找 马上回来
- We're getting him out of here. - Okay, I can do that. Be right back.
- 我们在这里等 - 我能帮什么忙吗？
- We'll wait here. - Is there something I can do to help?
我不知道
I don't know.
钥匙在哪？
Where are they?
莫达克家
Murdoch residence.
是 请稍候
Yes, just a second, please.
莫达克先生 尤金在在线
Mr. Murdoch, Eugene is on the phone.
莫达克
Murdoch.
- 我找到小屋了 - 然后呢？
- I found the cottage. - And?
你没提到蛇的事
You didn't say anything about the snake.
我说过他可能有几把刷子
Well, I told you he might have a few tricks up his sleeve.
这话言轻了
That's the understatement of the year.
我不知道会遇上这种事
I had no idea what we could expect.
一千万 干掉那个女的再加一百万
Ten million, and an extra million for taking out the girl.
别管那个女的了 你拿到血清了吗？
Forget the girl. Do you have the serum?
- 拿到了 - 很好
- Yes, I do. - Good.
叫你的人来找我
Tell your man to meet me.
我会准备好
I'll be ready.
搞定了 走吧
It's all set. Let's go.
温迪 没关系
Wendy. Wendy, it's okay, it's okay.
- 史考特来了 他有钥匙 - 好
- Scott showed up. He's got the keys. - Okay.
- 我想派崔克稳定了 - 好
- I think Patrick's stabilised. - Right.
我们拿了装备就离开
Let's grab our gear and get out of here.
- 我们现在就得离开 快 - 看着我…
- We have to leave now, come on. - Look at me. Look at me.
你是谁？
Who are you?
你刚才见到的东西我要负责 好吗？
I am responsible for what you saw back there, all right?
相信我 我们得离开这里
Trust me, we've gotta get out of here.
- 相信你？要我相信你？ - 没错
- Trust you? You want me to trust you? - Yeah.
你知道我们刚才看到什么？ 那是什么东西？
You know what we just saw out there? What is it?
- 某种实验？ - 没错
- Some kind of an experiment? - Exactly.
你看到的那些人是来拿血清的
Those men that you saw are here to get the serum.
- 什么血清？ - 他们不能留证人
- What serum? - They can't have any witnesses.
你懂我说的吗？我们必须离开
Do you understand? We have to get out of here.
- 他们会杀我们？ - 为何不？
- They would kill us? - Why not?
这是最利落的选择
It's the cleanest option.
她
Her.
你
You.
你对我的客户似乎有某种价值
You seem to be of a certain value to my client…
可以的话我要问你几个问题
…so I'm going to ask you a few questions, if I'm allowed.
这个给我
I'll take that.
我要找…
I'm looking for…
我要找血清 我相信你知道
I'm looking for a serum which I'm sure you know about.
抱歉
Sorry.
不要浪费时间
Don't. Don't waste my time.
告诉我这个人的事
Tell me about this man.
什么？我没听见
What? I didn't hear you.
再说一次
Tell me that again.
好 他是科学家 抓到一条蛇
Okay. He's a scientist that captured a snake.
好 他现在人呢？
Good. Where is he now?
- 回答问题 - 我不知道
- Answer the question. - I don't know.
我也在找他
I've been looking for him myself.
做什么？
To do what?
摧毁他创造的东西
To destroy everything that he's created.
我们走运 你还没 对吧？
Lucky for us, you didn't, right?
有那个东西在你们会很难拿到血清
It's gonna pretty be difficult for you to go get that serum with that thing.
- 谁？ - 你们要是尝试就会送命
- Who? - You guys are gonna die if you try.
既然如此 你去帮我们拿
If that's the case, you are going to go get it for us.
是吗？我为什么要那样做？
Really? Why would I do something like that?
- 嘿 - 派崔克
- Hey. - Patrick.
- 派崔克！ - 你做什么？
- Patrick! - What are you doing?
干嘛？我是帮他忙 他不用再受苦了
What? I make him a favour. He's not suffering anymore.
- 温迪 不要！ - 杰克森 不要
- Wendy, no! - Jackson, no.
- 温迪！ - 温迪 不要！
- Wendy! - Wendy, no!
- 不要！ - 杰克森 不要
- No! - Jackson, no.
- 杰克森 - 只要有机会
- Jackson. - I am gonna kill you…
我就杀了你
…the first chance I get.
- 杰克森 不要 - 放开他 我喜欢这样
- Jackson, no. - Let him go. I'm liking this.
- 听见没？你死定了 - 杰克森 不要
- You hear me? You are dead. - Jackson, no.
该死的 你… 天哪 为什么？
Damn you, you are… God. God, God, why?
- 杰克森 不要 - 天哪
- Jackson, no. - God.
嘿…嘿
Hey, hey, hey.
听好 你们两个十分钟内离开
Listen. You two, 10 minutes. You are leaving in 10 minutes.
你听到她说的 那东西会杀了我们
You heard what she said. That thing will kill us.
也许吧 但相信我
Maybe, but trust me…
你去的话 你跟你的组员 存活的机率比较大
…you and your team's chances of living are better if you go.
我会派我的人过去确认你们不会迷路
Now, I'll send my men to make sure you don't lose your way.
去吧
Go.
海瑟…过来…
Heather, Heather, come here, come here, come here.
有我在
I got you, I got you.
没事了…
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
没事了 我们走吧
It's okay, it's okay. Let's go, come on.
走吧 拜托跟我走
Come on. Please, just come with me.
陪着她让她冷静点 好吗？
Just stay with her. Just calm her down, okay?
有我在 我们走吧
Okay, I got you. Come on, we're gonna go.
我们走吧
Come on, let's go.
希望你们轻装便行
Hope you guys pack light…
以免我们要快速移动
…in case we gotta move fast.
- 你自己保重 小子 - 我会的
- Take care of yourself, kid. - I will.
- 你想我们能摆脱这一切吗？ - 说实话？可能没办法
- You think we'll get away with this? - Truth? Probably not.
我在这儿
I'm here.
我问你一件事
So let me ask you something.
这到底在研究什么？
What's this research about?
- 你真的想知道？ - 对 我真的想知道
- You really wanna know? - Yeah, I really wanna know.
长生不老 青春之泉
Longevity, immortality, the fountain of youth.
有人拿这种兰花加强其基因
Somebody took this orchid and genetically enhanced it…
当做血清的化学基础
…which is the chemical basis for the serum.
被注射血清的蛇 都能长到正常的一百倍大
Any snake that ingests this serum can grow 100 times its normal size.
- 而你在追蛇？ - 摧毁花和研究
- And you were chasing it? - Destroying the flowers and research…
是我弥补过错的唯一之道
…is the only way I could atone for what I did.
我每天都在等
I've been waiting every day…
带我找到这些兰花的任何迹象
…for any sign that would lead me to these orchids.
它们就在这里？
And this is where they were?
我开始听说奇怪的传言
I started hearing strange stories…
说这片山区有人和动物陆续失踪
…about these animals and people that were disappearing in these hills.
不用想也知道
Didn't take a genius to figure it out.
为什么要自己一个人来？
Why try it by yourself?
没人相信我
No one believed me.
有个叫瓦席里的警察跟着我 但是他死了
I had this cop, Vasile, with me, but he's dead.
- 抱歉 - 是啊
- Sorry. - Yeah.
找到了吗？
Find anything?
没有
No.
我想他藏在矿井里 在北边半里远
I think he hid it in the mineshaft, which is about a half a mile north.
你们想冒险吗？
You guys wanna chance it?
蛇是夜间动物 它们追踪热 外面很黑
Snakes are nocturnal. They detect heat. It's pretty dark out there.
除非你自认幸运
Unless you're feeling lucky.
我们在这里等到天亮
We'll wait here till sunup.
好 那我们继续找
Good. Then we'll keep looking.
我们究竟要找什么？
What exactly are we looking for?
跟血清有关的东西
Anything that references the serum.
（封锁）
嘿
Hey.
亲爱的 你得吃东西
Honey, you need to eat something.
海瑟 你看着我
Heather, look at me. Look at me.
我们有机会就离开这里
If we get the chance, we're getting out of here.
我只要你保持体力 因为我一个人办不到
And I need you to have your strength because I can't do this by myself.
我不会把你丢在这里
And I'm not leaving you here.
听见没有？我不会把你丢在这里
You hear me? I won't leave you here.
我不会丢下你
I'm not leaving you.
- 有结果吗？ - 没有 都是无聊的东西
- Anything? - No, it's all boring.
我在窗边放了炸弹
I just rigged an explosive to the window.
出不去也进不来
Nothing gets out, nothing gets in.
我们拖延不了他们多久
We're not gonna be able to stall these guys much longer.
最好在天亮前想出计划
We better have a plan before sunup.
松动的地板
Loose floorboards.
这是你在找的东西？
Is this what you're looking for?
- 底下还有吗？ - 没有 只有这个
- Is there any more down there? - No, that's it. Nothing else.
他一定把化学成份写在某个地方
He's gotta have the chemical composition written down somewhere.
如果那个东西会被花吸引
You know, if that thing's attracted to flowers…
它就会爱这个
…it's gonna love this.
知道吗？他们若找到这个
You know, they find this…
就会杀死我们
…they'll kill us both.
没错
Exactly.
血清会造成细胞再生
And that's the serum that causes cell regeneration.
什么意思？
What does that mean?
所以我们杀不死它
So we can't kill it.
开枪或砍头都不行
Not if you're talking about shooting it or cutting its head off.
它太大只了
It's too big.
但若内部器官有足够的伤害 或许可以
But if there's enough damage to the internal organs, maybe.
或许…
Maybe…
蛇的器官又细又长 因为它是长管状的 对吧？
The snake's organs are long and thin because of its tubular shape, right?
如果我们摧毁得够多它就不可能痊愈
If we destroy enough of them, there's no way it can heal.
不然就是把它活埋
Either that or burying it alive.
我没说这很容易
Hey, I didn't say this was gonna be easy.
血清就这么多 实在不合理
It just doesn't make sense that this would be all of the serum.
莫达克
Murdoch.
他不想让莫达克拿走
He didn't want Murdoch getting it…
所以把大部份都藏在别处
…so he would hide the bulk of it someplace else.
谁是莫达克？
Who's Murdoch?
莫达克就是出资造成这场梦魇的人
Murdoch's the one who financed this nightmare.
- 我要把它收起来以防万一 - 我们该睡了
- I'm gonna put this away just in case. - We should get some sleep.
搞什么鬼？
Hey, what's going on?
至少有人爽到了
At least somebody's having fun.
对不起
I'm sorry.
没关系
It's okay.
它嗅觉好吗？
How good is his smell?
没那么好 但这是浓缩液
Not that great, but this stuff is pure concentrate.
我出去一下
I'm stepping out.
快过来
Come here, quick.
好了吗？
Ready?
有什么计划？
So, what's the plan?
你知道吗 小子？我没有计划
You know what, kid? I don't have a plan.
我想时候到了就行动吧
I guess just be ready to move when I do.
万一我不在了…
And if I'm not here…
你就带她走 好吗？
…you bring her with you, okay?
好
Okay.
如果那个东西会被花吸引
You know, if that thing's attracted to flowers…
它就会爱这个
…it's gonna love this.
- 阿曼达 有什么计划？ - 我还在想
- Amanda, what's the plan? - I'm thinking, I'm thinking, I'm thinking.
- 阿曼达 有什么计划？ - 我在想！
- Amanda, what's the plan? - I'm thinking!
- 你要我怎样？ - 不要迁怒我 好吗？
- What do you want me to do, huh? - Don't take it out on me, all right?
我刚失去了三个朋友
I just lost three of my friends!
这是…你看 这是血清
This is… Look. It's the serum.
他一定是放在这里保持阴凉
He must have kept it in here to keep it cool.
很好 现在我们找到了
Great. Now we've found it.
只要回营地就行了
All we gotta do is get back to the camp.
嘿
Hey.
对不起
I'm sorry.
走吧
Come on.
- 我不知道往哪儿走 - 总之…
- I don't even know where we're going. - Well, just…
我们会有什么损失？
What do we got to lose, huh?
- 这边？ - 对
- This way? - Yeah.
你失去了几个朋友？
How many friends have you lost?
我现在没空聊那个 这不是我的任务
I can't really talk about that right now. It's not my mission.
- 这边 - 你确定？
- This way. - You sure?
- 确定 - 阿曼达！
- Yeah. - Amanda!
我们有血清 我们找到了
We have the serum. We actually… We found it.
拿去
Take it, take it.
- 有什么问题？ - 计划改变了
- Look, what's the problem? - There's been a change in plans.
- 我要自己去 - 把袋子给他
- I'll be going alone. - Give him the bag.
阿曼达 袋子给我
Amanda, hand me the bag.
- 阿曼达 袋子给他 - 你闭嘴
- Amanda, give him the bag. - Shut your mouth.
- 你退后 - 我们有你老板要的东西
- You, hey, back off. - We have what your boss asked for.
- 我们找到你老板要的东西 - 把袋子给他
- We found what your boss wants. - Give him the bag. Give him the bag.
- 退后 - 我们找到…
- Back off. - We found it in the…
- 快把袋子给我 - 阿曼达 袋子给他！
- Hand me the bag now. - Amanda, give him the bag!
快跑！
Run!
快
Go.
- 快点 - 快
- Come on. - Go.
- 你在干嘛？ - 你快跑
- What are you doing? - Go, run.
- 你在干嘛？不要！ - 你快跑
- What are you doing? No! - Run. Get out.
- 跟我走 - 快！快跑
- Come with me. - Go! Run, go.
很高兴见到您 先生
Glad to see you, sir.
尤金
Eugene.
你 回屋里去
You, back inside.
我要拿水给那女孩喝 她抽筋了
I need water for the girl. She's having convulsions.
没关系 我看着他
It's fine, I'll watch him.
- 路上还好吗？ - 糟透了
- How was the drive, sir? - Terrible.
- 有我该知道的事吗？ - 没有 一切都很好
- Is there anything I should know about? - No, sir, everything is good.
好
Good.
瓦席里？
Vasile?
你在这儿做什么？ 我叫你干掉那个女的
What are you doing here? I told you to take care of the girl.
我们走散了
We got split up.
你那条蛇差点害死我
That snake of yours almost killed me.
但它没有
But he didn't.
你又留下烂摊子了
Now you're just another loose end.
我有预感你会这样做
I had a feeling that's what you would do.
所以我谈了新合约
So I cut a new deal…
对方愿意付我两倍的钱
…with someone who will pay twice what you pay.
尤金 你派上用场了 准备开始清理门户吧
Eugene, this is what I pay you for. Time to start cleaning house.
其实…
Actually…
我就是他说的新伙伴
…I'm the new partner he was telling you about.
- 我们讲好条件了 - 很抱歉 莫达克
- But we had a deal. - I'm deeply sorry, Murdoch.
- 是很好的条件 - 开枪
- A very good deal. - Shoot him.
杀了他
Shoot him.
快呀
Go ahead.
你还在等什么？开枪
What are you waiting for? Shoot him.
快 我带你出去 我们走
Come on, let's get you out of here. We gotta go, come on.
扶她上吉普车 快
Get her to the car. Get her to the Jeep. Go, go, go.
动作快
Move, move, move. Go.
你还好吧？
Are you okay?
- 我想不太好 - 好吧 跟我走
- No, I don't think so. - Okay, come with me.
它们来了
They're coming.
- 我们快离开这里 - 没那么快 阿曼达
- We gotta get out of here. Come on. - Not so fast, Amanda.
莫达克
Murdoch.
我要是想杀你 你早就死了
If I wanted to kill you, you would already be dead.
这是全自动武器 你打算冒险吗？
Now, this is a fully automatic weapon. Are you prepared to take the risk?
对 试试看
Yeah, try me.
把我要的东西给我
Give me what I came for.
没那个闲功夫 那些蛇还活着
There's no time for this. The snakes are alive.
那些蛇？
Snakes?
彼得创造了一条会再生的蛇
Peter created a snake that would regenerate.
- 所以血清奏效了 - 威胁也加倍
- Then the serum works. - The threat has doubled.
真麻烦 但那不是当务之急
Oh, that's disturbing, but not of immediate concern.
嘿
Hey.
我们来谈条件
I'll give you a deal.
你们的命换血清
Your lives for the serum.
我说话算话
I am a man of my word.
是啊
Yeah.
快点
Come on.
给他吧
Just give it to him. Give it to him.
好吧 把你该死的血清拿去
All right. Take your bloody serum.
你们救了我的命
You saved my life.
现在逃命去吧
You can have yours. Now go.
快走
Go.
走啊 快走
Go on, get out.
快走
Go.
它要来了 动作快
It's coming, come on. Come on, hurry.
成功了！成功了！
It works! It works!
我要是五分钟没回来 就不会回来了
If I'm not back in five minutes, I'm not coming back.
好了
Made it.
你下地狱吧
You can rot in hell.
快 我们走
Come on, we gotta go.
- 杰克森 过来 - 好 我来了
- Jackson, come here. - Yeah, here, here, here.
- 钥匙拿去 你开车 - 好
- Here, take the keys. You drive. - Okay.
- 天哪 那是什么？ - 是大蟒蛇
- Oh, my God, what is that? - It's the anaconda.
我们走 快
Let's go, hurry.
开车 快
Drive, go.
快点…
Go, go, go.
把这个丢出窗外
Here, get rid of this. Throw it out the window.
- 趴下！ - 趴下…！
- Down! - Get down, down, down!
阿曼达 你没事吧？海瑟 趴下去
Amanda. Amanda, are you okay? Heather, stay down. Down.
艾力克斯 握住方向盘！
Alex, take the wheel!
艾力克斯 快握住方向盘！
Alex, take the damn wheel!
握住
Take it.
好了
Okay, come on.
我握住了
I got it.
杰克森！
Jackson!
眼睛看路
Keep your eyes on the road.
- 杰克森 - 不要
- Jackson. - No.
快点
Hurry.
- 快啊 杰克森 - 我在试啊
- Hurry, Jackson. - I'm trying.
我看你还怎么再生
Let's see you try and regenerate from that.
- 我们走吧 - 我们走
- Let's get out of here. - Let's go.